{
      "name": "Reizināšana ar 3",
      "level": 1,
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 13,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 1?",
          "correctAnswer": 3,
          "options": [2, 3, 4, 5]
        },
        {
          "id": 14,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 2?",
          "correctAnswer": 6,
          "options": [5, 6, 7, 8]
        },
        {
          "id": 15,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 3?",
          "correctAnswer": 9,
          "options": [6, 8, 9, 10]
        },
        {
          "id": 16,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 4?",
          "correctAnswer": 12,
          "options": [10, 11, 12, 13]
        },
        {
          "id": 17,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 5?",
          "correctAnswer": 15,
          "options": [12, 14, 15, 16]
        },
        {
          "id": 18,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 6?",
          "correctAnswer": 18,
          "options": [16, 18, 20, 21]
        },
        {
          "id": 19,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 7?",
          "correctAnswer": 21,
          "options": [20, 21, 22, 24]
        },
        {
          "id": 20,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 8?",
          "correctAnswer": 24,
          "options": [22, 23, 24, 25]
        },
        {
          "id": 21,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 9?",
          "correctAnswer": 27,
          "options": [25, 26, 27, 28]
        },
        {
          "id": 22,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 10?",
          "correctAnswer": 30,
          "options": [28, 29, 30, 31]
        },
        {
          "id": 23,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 11?",
          "correctAnswer": 33,
          "options": [32, 33, 34, 35]
        },
        {
          "id": 24,
          "type": "multiple-choice",
          "prompt": "What is 3 × 12?",
          "correctAnswer": 36,
          "options": [34, 35, 36, 37]
        }
      ]
    }